[upbeat techno music plays]
♪♪
[cheerful music plays]
[schwing!]
-Welcome back, my candy hearts
and paper flowers!
[schwing!]
-[grunts]
-Well, that sure
could have gone better.
But I'm sure the next
adventure will be less...
uh, wet.
-[Kinger]: Hey, Ragatha?
Can you help me
count my eggs before they hatch?
-Oh, yeah, of course.
Uh -- Wait, what?
-Looks like that
oh-so-positive Ragatha charm
is starting to wear off, huh?
-[groans]
-Hmm.
Hmm...
-[Zooble]: Looks like this one
was a home run, eh?
-Oh, Zooble,
you mismatched cash-piano.
I'll tear YOU TO PIECE--
Constructive criticism
would be greatly appreciated.
-[Zooble]:
But never acknowledged.
-[growls]
That's it!
Everybody besides Zooble,
get over here!
[mystical shimmering]
Everyone, I'm going to pitch to you
some future adventure ideas,
and I'm going to ask you to give me
your honest opinions on them.
-I was gonna sleep.
-All right!
So, I've got an adventure
where you all tour
my amazing
magic chocolate factory
and get killed off one by one
from OSHA violations,
one where a sentient
cardiovascular system
goes to war against
the United States military,
and one where you have to survive
in a post-apocalyptic nuclear wasteland
with a telepathic talking dog
who's mean to you the whole time!
What do you think?
-Uh, I don't know.
They all sound a little...
uh, dark?
-I can't tell a compelling story
where nothing bad happens.
Where's the intrigue?
The stakes?
-Not to mention
the sssssex appeal.
-What are you talking about?
-[Zooble]: You know, you could always
try the suggestion box again.
I honestly didn't hate
the last one we did with it.
-You... didn't hate it?
-[Zooble]: It was kind of refreshing
doing something grounded in reality.
-Yeah, I really didn't
mind that one, either.
-Uh, what about the rest of you?
[overlapping chatter]
-[Jax]: I very much did not
enjoy that one in the slightest,
and if we ever do anything
even close to that again,
I'm getting violent,
and I'm going to kill Ragatha.
-Well, how am I gonna please everybody
if you all like different things?
-[Zooble]: Maybe just keep
your adventures open at all times
and let us do whatever we want,
when we want.
-Are you hearing this, Bubble?
The toybox character wants us
to leave the other intelligent AIs
to run for a prolonged
period of time.
-Disgusting!
-[Zooble]: Am I not supposed
to be hearing you?
-Zippy!
[zip!]
-[Zooble]: What did you even zip up?
I don't have a mouth.
-Okay, well, how about this?
We'll do a lightning round,
going through all the suggestions
in the suggestion box
in rapid succession.
And if you don't like one,
you can all vote to skip it.
-What? Like, now?
-That's right!
So, grab your bones
and pop your pansies,
'cause here we go!
-Wait, didn't we just finish an adventure?
-I was gonna sleep!
[dramatic music plays]
Oh, wait, I know what this is!
-[Zooble]:
Oh, I swear to God,
if this is one
of your suggestions...
-Hi, everyone!
In today's episode
of "Poach Everything,"
I'm going to be hunting
the critically endangered
red ribbon rhinoceros.
Ahh, just like mom
used to make.
[cheerful musical sting plays]
[growling]
-[Zooble]: Oh, my God.
-Ahh, delicious meat.
One down, four to go!
-[Zooble]: All right, I'm calling a vote.
Let's skip this one --
and also make Jax a vegan
for the rest of the day.
-You can't do that.
[high-pitched tones chiming]
[buzzer blats]
[ding!]
What do you mean,
you can do that?
-Sorry, Jax --
democracy has spoken.
-Democracy sucks.
[portal shimmering]
-[Pomni]: Wait, what?
Why me?
-[Jax]: Eh, I thought
a position of power suited you.
-[Zooble]: Oh, my God,
are these all gonna be Jax's ideas?
[patriotic music plays]
-[Kinger]:
Well, Ms. President,
it looks like there are
some new developments
in the ongoing war
between Australia and New Zealand.
We may need
to take in some refugees.
What do you think?
-Wh-- How do you know what to do?
What?
-[Kinger]: Didn't you get the brief?
-I am...
just being here.
-You're doing great, Pomni!
-[Kinger]: Come down here for a sec.
[whispering]
We all got briefs on our characters.
I'm your assistant.
-I-Is that a baby-head lamp?
-[Kinger]:
Didn't you get one, too?
I figured we were all
on the same page here.
But, if not, you're gonna have to
tap into those golden improv skills.
-I'm sorry, what?
-[Jax]: Oh, yeah!
I didn't give you one
'cause I wanted to see what you'd do!
-Thanks, Jax.
Appreciate it.
-[Kinger]: I'm not Jax.
-[Australian accent]
Oy, mate!
I'm an Australian extremist,
and I've come
to detonate this bomb
that'll release all the world's
deadliest spiders into...
[normal voice]
Did I pick a bad time?
[canned laughter plays]
[laughter continues over speakers]
-His acting is phenomenal.
It's hard to believe he's vegan.
-Why wouldn't the president
have a bomb squad?!
-Don't worry,
President Pomni!
I believe you can do this.
-There's centipedes in there, too.
-Just be sure
you know what you're doing.
-Okay, well,
which wire do I cut?
-Follow your heart.
-You stay out of this!
Shouldn't you be arrested,
or something?
-Hey, I'm on your side here.
-You're literally not.
-Come on,
just pick your favorite color.
-Like the red one?
-[Kinger]:
I'd personally go with blue.
Blue's my favorite color --
it being closest
to black, and all.
-Wouldn't black be
your favorite color, then?
-[Kinger]: Well, no.
There's no black wire.
-Hi.
I'm a New Zealand
extremist, and...
I... don't..
know what New Zealanders
threaten people with.
[bomb ticking]
[mellow jazz music plays]
♪♪
-[distorted feedback blares]
[cheerful pop music plays]
-[Singer]: [singing in Japanese]
♪♪
-What is this?
I don't like this.
-[Zooble]: [sighs]
Can it.
At least we finally have one
that's by someone else.
-Yeah, there's nothing more fun
than being back in school.
-Just give it a chance, Jax.
Jeez.
-[Zooble]: There's nothing wrong
with your suggestion.
-Wh-- H-How did you know
this was my suggestion?!
-Can you believe this, Pomni?
First she draws anime.
Now she drags us all into one.
[scoffs]
She must be one of them, uh...
losers.
-You threw me out of a moving truck.
-[Kinger]: All right, class.
Today, we're gonna learn the popular
foreign language known as...
English?
-This is boring.
I vote we skip it.
-[Zooble]: Shut up, we're not skipping it.
-[scoffs] Slice-of-life animes
are the worst ones.
It's embarrassing!
[chuckles] I mean,
I guess it's not as embarrassing
as that time Gangle took
an anime figure and --
-Actually, yeah!
We can skip it, that's fine!
Let's skip this one!
[mellow celestial music plays]
[insects chirping softly]
♪♪
-Are we just chilling for this one?
Can I finally relax?
-Uh, I guess so.
But, uh, I prefer
a little bite to my adventures.
-[Kinger]: [chomps]
Then why don't you
help yourself to a sangwidge?
-[Zooble]: Here.
-Thanks.
-Do you think Gangle
is actually capable of being happy?
-What?
-I dunno.
Like, her comedy mask
still breaks every day.
Does she think hanging out with Zooble
is gonna magically fix that?
-Maybe she just
doesn't wanna hang out
with someone who's
mean to her all the time.
-She likes when
I'm mean to her, though.
-I didn't think you cared
about what other people like.
-[scoffs]
I just...
No, yeah, y-you're right --
I don't.
-Do you have any...
actual friends?
-Not anymore.
Oh -- Oh.
Oh, wait, no.
Uh, I'm -- I'm sorry.
I-I wasn't talking about --
That --That wasn't
meant to be --
Uh -- Uh...
Hey, Kinger!
[laughs awkwardly]
Did you see the fireflies
all the way over there?
-[Kinger]: [gasps]
Where?!
-What was that about?
-It's nothing.
Who cares?
[sighs] Doesn't she get
on your nerves sometimes?
-I mean, she's nice to everyone.
-[sighs]
I don't know, I just --
I think she tries way too hard.
Like, we're stuck in --
Why are you always pretending
everything's always fine?
Like, if you tell someone they're loved
and appreciated every day,
it just kind of loses all meaning.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
It just feels like she's trying
to take advantage of you, you know?
I don't know.
Also, she's dumb,
and she looks weird.
-Eh, I think we all look weird.
-[scoffs]
Excuse you.
This is what peak
male performance looks like.
My ears and tail are kind of
the pinnacle of masculinity.
-You don't have a tail.
-[scoffs]
What are you talking about?
Yes, I do.
It's -- It --
What the --
Where's my tail?
How long have I
not had my tail?
-I have never seen you
with a tail.
-When would that have even...
[stammers]
♪♪
-They look happy.
-They do, don't they?
-You think after this,
maybe we could --
-Wait a minute!
That's a bad thing!
-Explain to daddy Bubble
how bad thing?
-I-I think that --
Don't say that.
I-I think they're enjoying
the suggestion box adventures
more than the me adventures!
What should I do?
-You should die --
You should throw
a [BLEEP!] beach party!
-Why do you swear now?
Ugh, forget it.
Let's go to an intermission.
[rewound audio warbles]
-[deep sultry voice]:
Intermission time.
[record scratches]
[trippy music plays]
[remixed vocals play]
♪♪
-[Zooble]: Caine,
what are we doing right now?
-We're intermissioning!
-[Zooble]: Why?
Uh...
Hello?
-And now,
back to the show!
[moody jazz music plays]
[bell jingles]
♪♪
-Gimme a whiskey sour.
But hold the egg white,
since I'm a vegan.
Wha-- I hate this!
How is this even possible?
I thought Caine couldn't --
-[Zooble]: I could have
made it way worse for you.
-Well, I'm calling a vote
to turn Zooble into a slug.
[warbling tones play]
[low tones play]
-Everyone voted against that.
-UUUUGGHH!!
No hate it...
[bell jingles]
-[Kinger]: Phew!
It's raining like the dickens out there.
-Hey, guys.
♪♪
I'll have a cosmopolitan.
-[Kinger]:
Gimme a corncob blitz.
-[Zooble]:
I'll throw something together.
-You know your way
around alcohol, huh?
-[Zooble]: Yeah.
This was one of my suggestions.
I worked at a bar briefly.
I like making drinks.
-[scoffs]
That sounds fitting for you.
-[Zooble]: I know
there's an implication there,
but I can't be [BOINK!]
to figure it out.
-So, Pomni,
you ever have any jobs?
Or are you too young for that?
-I'm 25 years old.
And, yeah.
I was an accountant
for a -- a supermarket chain.
-A supermarket?
How'd you end up here?
-Well, I...
sometimes got bored of things...
and I would seek out mild thrills.
Like exploring
abandoned buildings, you know?
And posting videos of it online.
-Ah, a YouTuber.
-Not really.
Nobody watched them.
It was just something
I did for me.
-[Zooble]: I sometimes did that.
I wouldn't record it, though.
Here's your cosmo.
-Thanks.
-Hiding something.
-[Zooble]: You'd know
all about that, wouldn't you?
What's your story, then?
-Ah, I thought you'd never ask.
Well, after my
lung cancer diagnosis,
me and my junkie associate
from a chemistry class I used to teach --
-[Zooble]: I figured.
How about you, Gangle?
-Hey, I wasn't done.
-[Zooble]: If you're gonna
make [BOINK!] up,
at least be creative about it.
I know what you're referencing.
-Was that a reference
to something?
-Uh...
I worked in fast food.
-[Zooble]: You've done more than that.
What about your art?
-I was in community college
for graphic design,
but I dropped out.
I didn't really
pursue art much after that.
-[Zooble]: Hey, I'm always down
to make art together, if you want.
-Oh, I didn't know
you were an artist, too, Zooble.
-[Zooble]: Uh, yeah,
I was a tattoo artist for a couple years.
-A bartender AND a tattoo artist?
[laughs]
You're killin' me here, Zoobie.
-[Zooble]: What do you mean
when you say that?
Do you have, like,
an actual point?
Or are you just talking?
-I'm just havin' fun.
I forgot you hate fun.
-[Zooble]:
Fun isn't the thing I hate.
-I guess I'll go now.
Oh, jeez, where to start.
[laughs nervously]
Um, I was born
into a fairly wealthy family.
We had a large property
with horses and chickens.
And my mother...
Uh, well...
my mother was...
a lot.
Uh, I worked
in real estate for a bit
until I ended up...
here.
[sighs]
I'm sure she doesn't miss me.
I certainly don't
miss the yelling...
and the berating...
and guilt-tripping...
[laughs nervously]
And the...
Yeah. [laughs]
Just kind of a farm girl.
Nothing too out of the ordinary.
♪♪
-And no point in asking Kinger,
'cause there's no way
he remembers anything.
-[Kinger]: Never better!
-Do you guys know about his wife?
-Huh?
-[Kinger]: MY WHAT?!
Oh.
-[scoffs]
[door opens]
[bell dings]
-[NPC]: He--
-What?
-[Zooble]: That's disappearing guy.
That's just what he does.
-I see.
From a previous adventure?
-Yeah.
God, Pomni.
You didn't know that?
-[Zooble]: I'm ignoring you.
-By the way, Pomni,
sorry about the whole
president thing.
I just thought it'd be funny.
-Uh, are -- are --
are you apologizing?
What's happening?
-[Zooble]: Just ignore him.
-Uh...
Apology accepted.
I guess.
-Wow, the first steps
of a budding friendship.
Right, Ragatha?
-Uh, hey, Pomni.
Remember when Kaufmo
smashed me against the walls
and I got all jumbled up?
Ah, all things considered,
that was pretty funny, right?
-Noooo?
Not really.
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, sorry.
That was probably
pretty traumatic for you.
-Ooh, remember when
you got high at McDonald's
and told Gangle to kill herself?
[chuckles]
Now that was funny.
-What?
I-I did not say that!
I-I think.
No.
No, of course I didn't.
I -- And I am still so,
so sorry about that, Gangle.
I would never have
said anything like that
if I didn't get that
stupid sauce in my eye!
-Jeez, Raggy, just let yourself
be mean sometimes.
It's funny.
-[Zooble]: Yeah.
Constantly tormenting Gangle's
really funny, Jax.
-You guys all take this place
way too seriously.
Wh-- What is this?
Why'd you do that?
Can you get that thing
away from me?
-[Zooble]:
Are you afraid of corn?
-No.
Who's afraid of corn?
[exclaims]
-I'm bored!
Let's go to the next adventure!
-[Zooble]: You're not even a part of --
[crowd cheering]
-[Caine]: [through microphone]
It's softball, ladies and gentlemen!
-[Ragatha]: O-Oh.
We're doing this now?
-Beautiful night for a game,
right, Bubble?
-BLEEEH!!
-We've got the Big Tops
playing against
the Evil Big Tops!
-'Sup, [BLEEP!]?
I'm Evil Pomni.
-[cackling]
I'm Evil Ragatha!
-[Evil Kinger]:
Coach Dictatorer, here!
-[nervously]
Uh, hi, guys.
I-I'm Evil Jax.
-[Evil Orbsman]:
Evil Orbsman, reporting for duty!
-[Evil Zooble]: [goofy voice]
I'm Bazooble! [babbles]
-Well, that wasn't
in my suggestion.
-Why don't I get an evil clone?
-But first,
let's welcome our special guest,
here to sing
the American national anthem.
[crowd cheering]
[microphone feedback squeals]
-[Disappearing Guy]:
♪ Oh, sa-- ♪
[applause]
-[screams]
-[Kinger]: All right, team!
I may not know what's going on
or who is going on,
or when is going on,
or why is going on,
but I do know
where is going on,
and it's out on that field.
So, let's go break
some tailbones, team.
-H-Hey, guys.
-I-I hope we all have a fun game,
no matter who ends up winning.
-I wanna kill that guy.
-Well, hello, Stupidgatha!
I hope you're ready
to get completely annihilated!
[cackles]
Nobody loves you,
and you're going to die someday!
[cackles]
-We can't exactly die.
That's like the whole thing here.
-[Evil Orbsman]:
What the frick?
-Huh?
Oh, check this [BLEEP!] out.
You're out, dumb-[BLEEP!]
-[BOINK!] it!
-Hah! Get owned!
-[BLEEP!] yeah,
that's what I'm sayin'.
-Ah, she's cool.
Wait, w-what's that?
[chime rings]
What the heck?!
Who did this?!
-[giggles]
-YOU!
-[screaming]
-[Zooble]: Hey!
-[wailing]
-[Kinger]: Jax, you're up to bat!
-I cant -- Don't wanna --
[stammers]
I look like this, though!
-[Zooble]:
Seems fitting for you, though.
I figured you'd be into this.
-What does that mean?
What's that supposed to mean?
-[Zooble]: I'm just havin' fun.
I forgot you hate fun.
-I don't want to wear this!
[breathing heavily]
-[Zooble]: I have never seen you
this upset about something.
-[Kinger]: Jax! Bat!
-I'm gonna kill you
when this is over.
-[Evil Zooble]:
Let's see what you're made of!
-Sh-- Shut up!
-D-Don't worry!
I think you look good!
-I don't want to hear that!
I want you dead!
-[chomps]
-Huh, I guess there's no more ball.
We're done.
-[Kinger]: Wait!
I got this!
Hmm.
-[Zooble]: Wh-- Hey!
-[Kinger]: Sorry, Zooble.
It's just the perfect
regulation softball size.
We're not playin' baseball, here.
-[sighs]
I'm not doing this anymore.
-[Kinger]: Wait, Jax!
Wh-- What about
where is going on?
-[sighs] I can't believe
I hit it right to her.
I'm supposed to be
better than that.
[sighs]
Sorry.
I should be a better sport.
-Not to, like,
agree with Jax, or anything,
but there's nothing wrong with
showing your negative emotions.
That's... pretty normal.
-[sighs]
I don't know.
I don't want to be
a jerk, or anything.
-I think we all need
to be a jerk sometimes.
-[mumbles]
Maybe.
Who knows?
-[Zooble]: Caine!
We need a ball here!
-[snores] [stammers]
Wha--
Oh!
[schwing!]
-[Zooble]:
Jax, we have a ball now!
What are you doing?
-Ugh, see ya.
Whoops, I missed.
Oh, darn, I'm out.
-Having fun?
-Oh, you know it.
Oh, look, Gangle's up to bat.
How do you think this is gonna go?
-Would you stop trying
to force her to act like you?
-Oh, yeah, I should
force her to be happy
all the time instead -- right.
-Well, it's better than turning her
into some insensitive jerk
who deflects everything.
-I can think for myself, guys.
-Hey, I ain't forcin'
anything on ya.
-And then you just act like
you never do anything wrong
and everybody loves you,
when, in reality,
you just [BONK!] everything up
for everyone else!
-Okay, let's, like,
calm down a bit.
-What?!
You're the one who said
it's fine to be a jerk sometimes!
Ugh!
I'm sorry, Pomni.
[sighs]
That wasn't very cool of me.
-I-It's fine.
-No apologies for me?
This is so sad.
-[sighs]
I'm sorry, Jax...
for...
for bringing up that thing earlier.
-So...
You wanna...
talk about that?
-I'm in a maid outfit.
What do you think?
[yelps]
-[sighs]
So, how's the game going?
-[Kinger]: Great!
Gangle hit a home run!
-Really?
-Yeah.
Your instructions helped me a lot.
-Huh.
[laughs softly]
-[Zooble]: Can you give me
my eye back?
-[Evil Zooble]: Jokes on you --
I've already forgotten
what you're talkin' about!
[grunts]
-Wowie!
Another home run!
-[Evil Kinger]:
God [BLEEP!]
-[Zooble]: What, uh --
Okay.
-[Kinger]:
Nice going, Zooble!
All right, Pomni, you're up.
-Hey, Ragatha?
You wanna bat for me instead?
-O-O-Oh, uh...
I guess I could,
if you really don't want to.
-Think of it as a --
a second chance
to show 'em who's boss.
-[chuckles]
Yeah.
Uh...
-Bazowieezooweewa!
Another home run!
And that makes three
home runs in a row!
The Big Tops win!
-Uh, that's...
not how softball works.
-Well, that's how my softball works.
We're done!
Hooray!
-No!
[shrieking]
-Ugh.
[BLEEP!], man.
We didn't even get to bat.
-[Kinger]: You did it, Ragatha!
-Whoa!
-[Kinger]: We won!
-Uh, I mean, I guess.
[laughs]
-Good job --
whatever you did.
-[Zooble]: Huh?
Uh, oh, yeah.
Good job, team.
-Huh?
Oh, cool.
I'm not a vegan anymore.
-Oh, hey!
W-Wait, what are you --
-[growling]
-[screaming]
-[Kinger]:
Why is going on?!
[screaming and growling continue]
[portal shimmering]
-Well, I hope we all learned
that suggestion box ideas
are actually not fun at all,
and Caine's ideas
are much better!
-[Zooble]: Well, some of them
were pretty okay.
-I kind of liked
the low-stakes ones.
-I thought the first two
were awesome.
The rest, eh.
Oh, yeah, Pomni -- I can show you that
thing in the hall I was talking about.
-Uh, oh, yeah, sure.
-[sighs]
[sinister music plays]
♪♪
[upbeat jazzy music plays]
[Captioned by Foulweather Studios]
♪♪